{
    "subject":"Christain Religious Studies",
    "topics":
    [
        {
            "topic":"Obedience/Disobedience",
            "questions":
            [
                {
                    "question":"amongst whom of these people obeyed God's commandments",
                    "opt1":"David",
                    "opt2":"Saul",
                    "opt3":"Pharoah",
                    "opt4":"Namaan",
                    "ans":"David"
                },
                {
                    "question":"Obedience is better than",
                    "opt1":"Call",
                    "opt2":"Death",
                    "opt3":"Sacrifice",
                    "opt4":"Maturity",
                    "ans":"Sacrifice"
                },

                {
                    "question":"Faith leads to obedience",
                    "opt1":"True",
                    "opt2":"False",
                    "opt3":"Maybe",
                    "opt4":"I don't know",
                    "ans":"True"
                },
                {
                    "question":"Samuel was obedient to Eli",
                    "opt1":"True",
                    "opt2":"False",
                    "opt3":"Maybe",
                    "opt4":"I don't know",
                    "ans":"True"
                },
                {
                    "question":"Who obeyed God and left his homeland to where God showed him/her",
                    "opt1":"Ruth",
                    "opt2":"Abraham",
                    "opt3":"Nehemiah",
                    "opt4":"Samuel",
                    "ans":"Abraham"
                },
                {
                    "question":"Did Solomon ever betray God",
                    "opt1":"Yes",
                    "opt2":"No",
                    "opt3":"Maybe",
                    "opt4":"I don't know",
                    "ans":"Yes"
                }
                
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic":"The Creation Story",
            "questions":
            [
                {
                    "question":"The job of giving names to all animals was for",
                    "opt1":"adam",
                    "opt2":"eve",
                    "opt3":"man",
                    "opt4":"adam and eve",
                    "ans":"adam"
                },
                {
                    "question":"Pishon,Gihon,Nile and Euphrates were divided into the garden of Eden",
                    "opt1":"True",
                    "opt2":"False",
                    "opt3":"Maybe",
                    "opt4":"I don't know",
                    "ans":"False"
                },

                {
                    "question":"The fact that all thing that God said should happen actually happened during creation means",
                    "opt1":"God is sovereign over the universe",
                    "opt2":"God is all knowing",
                    "opt3":"God is nice to all",
                    "opt4":"God did not like darkness",
                    "ans":"God is sovereign over the universe"
                },
                {
                    "question":"The second account of creation was centered on the creation of",
                    "opt1":"man",
                    "opt2":"plant",
                    "opt3":"firmament",
                    "opt4":"birds",
                    "ans":"man"
                },
                {
                    "question":"Eve is called woman why?",
                    "opt1":"She was taken out of man",
                    "opt2":"She was the author of wos",
                    "opt3":"She loves nature",
                    "opt4":"She caused God to banish them",
                    "ans":"She was taken out of man"
                },
                {
                    "question":"The firmament of heaven was created on which day",
                    "opt1":"Second",
                    "opt2":"Third",
                    "opt3":"Fourth",
                    "opt4":"Sixth",
                    "ans":"Second"
                }
                
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic":"Leadership",
            "questions":
            [
                {
                    "question":"Why did Reuben advise his brothers to throw Joseph into a pit and not kill him",
                    "opt1":"He loved his brother dearly",
                    "opt2":"He wanted to rescue him and bring him to this father",
                    "opt3":"For selfish reasons",
                    "opt4":"The reason was unknown",
                    "ans":"He wanted to rescue him and bring him to his father"
                },
                {
                    "question":"Who amongst the following was a leader",
                    "opt1":"Joshua",
                    "opt2":"Naomi",
                    "opt3":"Nehemiah",
                    "opt4":"Naboth",
                    "ans":"Joshua"
                },

                {
                    "question":"Who was a good leader among the following",
                    "opt1":"Nehemiah",
                    "opt2":"David",
                    "opt3":"Saul",
                    "opt4":"Bathsheba",
                    "ans":"David"
                },
                {
                    "question":"David was first crowned king of where",
                    "opt1":"hebron",
                    "opt2":"isreal",
                    "opt3":"judah",
                    "opt4":"judea",
                    "ans":"hebron"
                },
                {
                    "question":"Who was a bad leader among these",
                    "opt1":"David",
                    "opt2":"Solomon",
                    "opt3":"Ahab",
                    "opt4":"Deborah",
                    "ans":"Ahab"
                },
                {
                    "question":"Who delivered the people of Isreal from sisera",
                    "opt1":"God",
                    "opt2":"Deborah",
                    "opt3":"Jael",
                    "opt4":"Barak",
                    "ans":"Jael"
                }
                
            ]
        },
        {
            "topic":"The trial, death and resurrection of Jesus Christ",
            "questions":
            [
                {
                    "question":"Who betrayed Christ",
                    "opt1":"Judas Iscariot",
                    "opt2":"Judas",
                    "opt3":"Paul",
                    "opt4":"Pontius Pilate",
                    "ans":"Judas Iscariot"
                },
                {
                    "question":"Christ rose on the",
                    "opt1":"Third day",
                    "opt2":"Second day",
                    "opt3":"First day",
                    "opt4":"Fifth day",
                    "ans":"Third day"
                },

                {
                    "question":"Who did the people choose to release instead of Jesus",
                    "opt1":"Barrabas",
                    "opt2":"Barnabas",
                    "opt3":"The other theif on the cross",
                    "opt4":"Paul",
                    "ans":"Barrabas"
                },
                {
                    "question":"Who cut one of the guard's ears during the arrest of Jesus",
                    "opt1":"Paul",
                    "opt2":"Peter",
                    "opt3":"James",
                    "opt4":"Untold",
                    "ans":"Untold"
                },
                {
                    "question":"eli, eli lama saba e thani was said by Jesus on the cross",
                    "opt1":"True",
                    "opt2":"False",
                    "opt3":"Maybe",
                    "opt4":"I don't know",
                    "ans":"True"
                },
                {
                    "question":"Peter betrayed Jesus by denying him when?",
                    "opt1":"three times before the cock crows",
                    "opt2":"two times before the cock crows",
                    "opt3":"three times before he slept off",
                    "opt4":"three times before the twelfth hour",
                    "ans":"three times before the cock crows"
                }
                
            ]
        }
        
    ]
}
